I had an idea a show where four women
get together to talk mostly about their
mutual friend Janelle let's
gab oh they're cute thank you say
everybody have an exciting weekend oh
you know what I want to start because
Saturday I had a day oh what happened
all right well you know I was picking up
my new Rescue puppy Simon he God oh stop
you have to rescue there's no other way
on the way home ran in to guess
who don't tell me Janelle oh I knew it
Janelle okay so we're saying goodbye and
she kisses me on both cheeks like um I'm
sorry are you the Duchess of Brussels
all of a sudden yeah it's like uh
USA well Amy's already got us started so
I think we should just get right into it
our big issue
segment oh people love this love it okay
I have a huge issue with Janelle's
Facebook page oh who doesn't don't we
all hash hope this day never ends um
that's what days do jelle they end oh
and B uh we know his name's Steve like
you know she just wants to say
fiance like off about this dude MH
something is up something's up I
actually really like
him yeah but like come on oh yeah
totally he is weird we weird so weird
but we're on to our segment where we
check Janelle's Instagram oh my God this
is the best wow shocker it's about her
cat again like we get it it's fur makes
it look like it's wearing a tuxedo who
cares oh God do you know that that cat I
heard isn't even a rescue shut up she
bought it no yeah I knew it you know
where she got it the mall she got a
small cat oh my God that is so
disgusting oh my God you guys I just got
a DM from Janelle oh my God should we
read it uh it says heard about the new
show ladies I'm sure it's great cuz you
guys are the
best she knows I'm at work think I'm at
work it's like we're working we're
working all right you guys stay with us
cuz when we come back we'll be
interviewing Janelle's personal trainer
who she met with
once at least you
win okay do you want to be a part of
this
[Applause]
[Music]
show